[
    {
        "front": "くれます ❘❘",
        "back": "give (to me), (l recieve)",
        "chapter": "N5 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "つれていきます ❘",
        "back": "take along (someone)",
        "chapter": "N5 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "つれてきます ❘❘❘",
        "back": "bring along (someone)",
        "chapter": "N5 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "おくります ❘",
        "back": "escort (someone)",
        "chapter": "N5 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "しょうかいします ❘❘❘",
        "back": "introduce (someone)",
        "chapter": "N5 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "あんないします ❘❘❘",
        "back": "show around, show the way, guide",
        "chapter": "N5 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "せつめいします ❘❘❘",
        "back": "explain",
        "chapter": "N5 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "いれます ❘❘\n[コーヒーを]",
        "back": "make (coffee)",
        "chapter": "N5 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "おじいさん ／ おじいちゃん",
        "back": "grandfather, old man",
        "chapter": "N5 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "おばあさん ／ おばあちゃん",
        "back": "grandmother, old woman",
        "chapter": "N5 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "じゅんび",
        "back": "preparation",
        "chapter": "N5 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "いみ",
        "back": "meaning",
        "chapter": "N5 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "[お] かし",
        "back": "sweets, snacks",
        "chapter": "N5 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぜんぶ",
        "back": "all",
        "chapter": "N5 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "じぶんで",
        "back": "by oneself",
        "chapter": "N5 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "ほかに",
        "back": "besides, other than this",
        "chapter": "N5 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "ワゴンしゃ",
        "back": "station wagon",
        "chapter": "N5 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "[お] べんとう",
        "back": "box lunch",
        "chapter": "N5 C24"
    }
]